<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="link_policy">Push to view privacy policy</string>
    <string name="policyText">
POPmessage is especially sensitive in the protection of the users of the
data services which can be accessed through your website. Through this privacy policy
(henceforth, policy) POPmessage informs users of the APP: user of the
data treatment and applications that submit the personal data that is collected on the website,
in order to decide, freely and voluntarily, if they wish to provide the requested information.\n\n
POPmessage reserves the right to modify this policy in order to adapt it to new
legislative, jurisprudential criteria, practices, or interests of the entity. \n\n
Any modification in the same will be announced with due notice, to have perfect knowledge of its content.\n\n
Certain services provided on the website may contain conditions with provisions on the protection of personal data
. You can read in the corresponding sections of them.
\n\n\n
OWNERSHIP OF THE TREATMENT\n
In such cases, the data collected by POPmessage will be incorporated into files belonging to
POPmessage, duly registered in the General registry of data protection.
\n\n\n
USES AND PURPOSES\n
The purpose of the collection and processing of personal data is the management, delivery and customization
of the services and contents that the user uses and which will be informed in each section.
\n\n\n
COMMUNICATION OF DATAS\n
The data collected through the website only be disclosed in cases in which expressly informing
of this user.
\n\n\n
UPDATING DATA\n
In order that the data in our databases always correspond to your actual situation
must keep them updated, well updating them you directly in the case in which this is possible well communicating it to the relevant Department.
\n\n\n
UPDATING DATA\n
In order to protect the privacy of the users of the application POPmessage uses cookies when
them navigate it.
\n\n\n
DATA SECURITY\n
THE POPmessage has adopted in its information system the technical and organisational measures legally required,
in order to ensure the security and confidentiality of the stored data, thus avoiding
to the extent possible, their alteration, loss, treatment or unauthorized access.
\n\n\n
RIGHTS OF USERS\n
In any case you will be able to access your data, rectify them, cancel them and where appropriate, oppose your treatment:\n
Sending an e-mail to the following e-mail address: zonamessages@gmail.com
    </string>
</resources>